<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content>
    <news header="British players handed tough Australian Open draw as Draper faces Nadal" image_src="images/img.png">
        Great Britain’s men’s players have been handed a series of brutal first round draws at the Australian Open. In his first main draw appearance, Jack Draper will debut against defending champion and top seed Rafael Nadal on Rod Laver Arena.
        Meanwhile, Andy Murray has been drawn to face former Wimbledon finalist Matteo Berrettini in the opening round and Kyle Edmund, a former semi-finalist, will play the 15th seed Jannik Sinner.
    </news>
    <news header="Jack Draper stuns Karen Khachanov to continue promising Australian Open buildup" image_src="images/img_1.png" >
        On the eve of the Australian Open, one of the best weeks of Jack Draper’s young career continued with a 6-4, 7-6 (3) win over Karen Khachanov to reach the semi-finals of the Adelaide ATP 250 event.
        Draper’s victory sets up his second career ATP semi-final after his first in Eastbourne last June. Having defeated two successive seeds in Adelaide, Draper has offered himself a great opportunity to contest his first ATP final. He will next face either Mikael Ymer, a qualifier, or lucky loser Kwon Soonwoo.
    </news>
    <news header="Beyond the Kyrgios noise: other home hopes fly under the radar at Australian Open" image_src="images/img_2.png" >
        Up his second career ATP semi-final after his first in Eastbourne last June. Having defeated two successive seeds in Adelaide, Draper has offered himself a great opportunity to contest his first ATP final. He will next face either Mikael Ymer, a qualifier, or lucky loser Kwon Soonwoo.
        As former Australian Open tournament director Paul McNamee noted, the world No 24 has been able to go about his preparation for the year’s first major with a minimum of fuss. The reason? The hype surrounding Australia’s new Netflix sensation Nick Kyrgios, who is yet to play a point this year but will feature in a sell-out practice session against Novak Djokovic on Friday night on Rod Laver Arena.
        “Alex is under the radar because Nick is Nick,” McNamee said. “The rankings don’t lie. With Nick and Alex, it is great to have two guys who are going to be doing some stuff. “I mean Alex, you can’t fault his preparation. And the other guy has had no preparation, but that is par for the course and it doesn’t mean Nick won’t play great at Melbourne Park.”
        With Ajla Tomljanovic, a quarter-finalist at Wimbledon and the US Open last year, under an injury cloud, De Minaur and Kyrgios are the leading local hopes in the post-Ash Barty era.
        It is a year since Kyrgios and Thanasi Kokkinakis claimed the Australian Open doubles title, either thrilling or appalling fans depending on their appreciation of tennis traditions. No matter the opinion, there is no dispute the Special Ks were a headline act and with Kyrgios now a Wimbledon finalist and Kokkinakis back in form, both will carry strong support.
    </news>
    <news header="Aaron Rodgers has 59.5m reasons to play in the NFL in 2023. But will he?" image_src="images/img_3.png" >
        Draper’s victory sets up his second career ATP semi-final after his first in Eastbourne last June. Having defeated two successive seeds in Adelaide, Draper has offered himself a great opportunity to contest his first ATP final. He will next face either Mikael Ymer, a qualifier, or lucky loser Kwon Soonwoo.
        Not so fast. Rodgers spent his final seconds at Lambeau Field after the Packers’ disappointing 20-16 loss to the Detroit Lions on Sunday doing what he does best: Sending cryptic messages.
        Rodgers walked down the tunnel arm in arm with Randall Cobb, moving aside a videographer in order to absorb the moment with his pal. He declined to swap jerseys with Jameson Williams, telling the Lions receiver: “I’m gonna hold on to this one.” It doesn’t take Benoit Blanc to figure out Rodgers was hinting, again, at retiring.
    </news>
</content>
