<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content>
    <news header="British players handed tough Australian Open draw as Draper faces Nadal" image_src="images/img.png">
        Great Britain’s men’s players have been handed a series of brutal first round draws at the Australian Open. In his first main draw appearance, Jack Draper will debut against defending champion and top seed Rafael Nadal on Rod Laver Arena.
        Meanwhile, Andy Murray has been drawn to face former Wimbledon finalist Matteo Berrettini in the opening round and Kyle Edmund, a former semi-finalist, will play the 15th seed Jannik Sinner.
    </news>
    <news header="Jack Draper stuns Karen Khachanov to continue promising Australian Open buildup" image_src="images/img_1.png" >
        On the eve of the Australian Open, one of the best weeks of Jack Draper’s young career continued with a 6-4, 7-6 (3) win over Karen Khachanov to reach the semi-finals of the Adelaide ATP 250 event.
        Draper’s victory sets up his second career ATP semi-final after his first in Eastbourne last June. Having defeated two successive seeds in Adelaide, Draper has offered himself a great opportunity to contest his first ATP final. He will next face either Mikael Ymer, a qualifier, or lucky loser Kwon Soonwoo.
    </news>
    <news header="Beyond the Kyrgios noise: other home hopes fly under the radar at Australian Open" image_src="images/img_2.png" >
        Up his second career ATP semi-final after his first in Eastbourne last June. Having defeated two successive seeds in Adelaide, Draper has offered himself a great opportunity to contest his first ATP final. He will next face either Mikael Ymer, a qualifier, or lucky loser Kwon Soonwoo.
        As former Australian Open tournament director Paul McNamee noted, the world No 24 has been able to go about his preparation for the year’s first major with a minimum of fuss. The reason? The hype surrounding Australia’s new Netflix sensation Nick Kyrgios, who is yet to play a point this year but will feature in a sell-out practice session against Novak Djokovic on Friday night on Rod Laver Arena.
        “Alex is under the radar because Nick is Nick,” McNamee said. “The rankings don’t lie. With Nick and Alex, it is great to have two guys who are going to be doing some stuff. “I mean Alex, you can’t fault his preparation. And the other guy has had no preparation, but that is par for the course and it doesn’t mean Nick won’t play great at Melbourne Park.”
        With Ajla Tomljanovic, a quarter-finalist at Wimbledon and the US Open last year, under an injury cloud, De Minaur and Kyrgios are the leading local hopes in the post-Ash Barty era.
        It is a year since Kyrgios and Thanasi Kokkinakis claimed the Australian Open doubles title, either thrilling or appalling fans depending on their appreciation of tennis traditions. No matter the opinion, there is no dispute the Special Ks were a headline act and with Kyrgios now a Wimbledon finalist and Kokkinakis back in form, both will carry strong support.
    </news>
    <news header="Aaron Rodgers has 59.5m reasons to play in the NFL in 2023. But will he?" image_src="images/img_3.png" >
        Draper’s victory sets up his second career ATP semi-final after his first in Eastbourne last June. Having defeated two successive seeds in Adelaide, Draper has offered himself a great opportunity to contest his first ATP final. He will next face either Mikael Ymer, a qualifier, or lucky loser Kwon Soonwoo.
        Not so fast. Rodgers spent his final seconds at Lambeau Field after the Packers’ disappointing 20-16 loss to the Detroit Lions on Sunday doing what he does best: Sending cryptic messages.
        Rodgers walked down the tunnel arm in arm with Randall Cobb, moving aside a videographer in order to absorb the moment with his pal. He declined to swap jerseys with Jameson Williams, telling the Lions receiver: “I’m gonna hold on to this one.” It doesn’t take Benoit Blanc to figure out Rodgers was hinting, again, at retiring.
    </news>
    <news header="England produce strong finish to win series-opener against Jamaica" image_src="images/img_4.png" >
        Rodgers walked down the tunnel arm in arm with Randall Cobb, moving aside a videographer in order to absorb the moment with his pal. He declined to swap jerseys with Jameson Williams, telling the Lions receiver: “I’m gonna hold on to this one.” It doesn’t take Benoit Blanc to figure out Rodgers was hinting, again, at retiring.
        Jamaica dominated the opening quarter, with their captain and goal shooter, Jhaniele Fowler, putting in an impressive display to give her side a six-point lead in the first quarter.
        England began to creep back into the game in the second quarter, building up momentum and moving well, but Jamaica held firm to go into half-time with a 34-31 lead.
        Some solid defence from the centre Jade Clarke helped Jo Harten put the hosts in front after the break and in a tightly contested third quarter England edged ahead 49-47.
        The Vitality Roses then stormed ahead in the fourth quarter, reducing Jamaica to just five goals, as they secured a comprehensive victory.
    </news>
    <news header="Medvedev aims to arrest mini-slump with strong Australian Open showing" image_src="images/img_5.png" >
        “If there is a tournament on hard courts in Moscow, before Roland Garros or Wimbledon, I’m going to go there even if I miss the Wimbledon or Roland Garros or whatever. The kid stopped dreaming. The kid is going to play for himself.”
        In the immediate aftermath, Medvedev handled himself well. He continued his schedule as planned, only an injury during the clay season and Wimbledon’s decision to ban Russian players the only changes. In February, Medvedev rose to become the first world No 1 in 18 years other than Nadal, Novak Djokovic, Roger Federer or Andy Murray. He had backed up his triumph at the 2021 US Open and the Australian Open final that followed.
        Yet one of the stories of the months since has been how Medvedev has quietly slipped into a mini-slump. He was consistent throughout last year and at times played extremely well, reaching five finals, but he managed to win only two titles. Although he reliably navigated deep into draws on hard court and grass, he also consistently fell away in the biggest moments.
        As a result, Medvedev has fallen from No 1 to No 8. He is now the second-highest ranked player from Russia behind Andrey Rublev. Should he perform poorly in Melbourne, he could theoretically fall out of the top 10.
        On the court, Medvedev’s serve and usually impenetrable defence have become increasingly vulnerable. His ability to outlast almost every rival in long, attritional rallies, has evaded him in the big moments, error-free stretches replaced with too many mistakes. Since the Australian Open, Medvedev has lost in the fourth round of both slams he has played in.
        Last week, Medvedev won his first three matches of the season before facing Novak Djokovic in the semi-final in Adelaide, a match that seemed like a litmus test for both. Djokovic eased to a 6-3, 6-4 win.
    </news>
    <news header="Here’s the catch: cricket’s unique moment is being lost in all the angles" image_src="images/img_6.png" >
        Players at all levels go misty-eyed and weak at the knees when they try to describe it. If you’ve played the game at some point then maybe you’ve experienced it too? Can you guess?
        The pinched single on 99 to bring up a hard-earned hundred? Nope. The surge of joy upon hearing the ball scud into the stumps? Afraid not. That feeling that courses through hands, wrist and then gut when you connect with a ball so sweetly it soars for six? Nah.
        It’s the fraction of a second when a catch is taken and you know you’ve got it but no one else yet does. It’s still only between you and the ball, a secret shared in the liminal space. It’s there only for the merest flicker of time and then it’s gone, lost, punctured by ecstasy and euphoria. Maybe even relief.
        Don’t just take my word for it. Paul Collingwood took 96 catches in 68 Tests, including his fair share of cortex-boggling grabs. He will be better placed to describe it. “First you have that moment of seeing the ball and thinking: ‘Am I gonna get there? Am I no …? And then when you feel it actually almost kind of soak into to your hand. It’s just an incredible feeling.”
        The line goes quiet for a second and I can tell that I’ve briefly lost the flaxen-haired fielding great to his thoughts. He has floated off down the endless stream of spectacular catches in his mind.
        The same thing happens when speaking to the former England wicketkeeper Jack Russell, a career of moments and feelings flood back. “I took a ball down the leg-side one-handed in a cup final against Somerset, that one was … wow. I can feel it now. It sticks out above everything, that.”
    </news>

    <news header="Jofra Archer takes three wickets on long-awaited return to cricket" image_src="images/img_7.png" >
        It took three deliveries for Jofra Archer to remind the world of his wicket-taking abilities, as England’s injury-plagued fast bowler returned to competitive cricket after an absence of 541 days in the opening game of South Africa’s new domestic Twenty20 competition, the SA20.
        Archer took three wickets for 27 runs in his four overs as part of a three-pronged English bowling attack for MI Cape Town as they won by eight wickets against a Paarl Royals side that included Jos Buttler, Jason Roy and Eoin Morgan.
        “It’s super hard after having that long, long gap and then coming back, and that kind of comeback was absolutely delightful to watch,” the MICT captain, Rashid Khan, said. “We saw him in practice and the way he was bowling it was like: ‘He’s ready to go.’ It was super great to watch him – he is fully ready and it’s great that he’s back.”
        Archer had not played a T20 match since July 2021, but there was little evidence of any rustiness as he swung back into action with a wicket maiden, dismissing Wihan Lubbe with his third ball, caught at mid-on off a leading edge. He returned later in the innings to remove David Miller, the Royals captain, and Ferisco Adams with successive deliveries to conclude a heartening display.
        Olly Stone – whose own injury issues include four stress fractures of the back – took two wickets, including that of Buttler, who scored 51 off 42 balls before missing a slow-ball full toss and losing his middle stump. Sam Curran went wicketless, though his smart throw led to Morgan being run out off the final ball of the Royals innings.
    </news>
    <news header="‘A little life update for 2023’: Naomi Osaka announces pregnancy" image_src="images/img_8.png" >
        Naomi Osaka has provided context for her absence from this year’s Australian Open, posting a photo and text to Twitter announcing that she is pregnant with her first child.
        The 25-year-old tennis star and four-time grand slam champion posted a picture of a sonogram of a baby dated last month along with the message: “Can’t wait to get back on the court but here’s a little life update for 2023.”
        She also included screenshots of a statement in both English and Japanese in which she wrote: “These few months away from the sport has really given me a new love and appreciation for the game I’ve dedicated my life to.
        “I know that I have so much to look forward to in the future; one thing I’m looking forward to is for my kid to watch some of my matches and tell someone, ‘That’s my mom.’”
        Osaka officially withdrew from the Australian Open, which she has won twice, on Sunday, prompting questions and speculation over her absence. She added that she expected to return to Melbourne Park to take part in next year’s tournament.
        The former world No 1, who has also won the US Open on two occasions, last played a competitive match at the Toray Pan Pacific Open in Tokyo in September, where she won her opening match against Daria Saville before withdrawing ahead of her second-round tie with Beatriz Haddad Maia due to abdominal pain.
    </news>
</content>
